{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"5332","name":"Sliders LLC","address":"13330 W McNichols Rd","zipcode":"48235","owner":"Terrence Pritchett","licenseNumber":"229248","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":null,"riskCategory":"High","reviewFrequencyDays":"180","coords":"-83.17694,42.41686","geojson":{"id":"5332","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.176938738,42.416863417]},"properties":{"name":"Sliders LLC","owner":"Terrence Pritchett","address":"13330 W McNichols Rd","zipcode":"48235","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":"High","license_number":"229248","establishmentid":"5332","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":null,"review_frequency_days":"180","most_recent_license_date":"4/30/2018"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"4253","name":"Golden Bowl Chop Suey","address":"13337 W McNichols Rd","zipcode":"48235"},{"establishmentid":"2362","name":"Shirley Nelson's E & S Carryout","address":"13400 W McNichols Rd","zipcode":"48235"},{"establishmentid":"2361","name":"Kentucky Fried Chicken H730222","address":"13546 W McNichols Rd","zipcode":"48235"},{"establishmentid":"51623089","name":"Adams Young Academy","address":"13130 Grove St","zipcode":"48235"},{"establishmentid":"519","name":"Connie & Barbara Restaurant","address":"13101 W McNichols Rd","zipcode":"48235"},{"establishmentid":"5163","name":"Brown's Kitchen","address":"17150 Schaefer Hwy","zipcode":"48235"},{"establishmentid":"3582","name":"Lincoln-King Academy","address":"13436 Grove St","zipcode":"48235"},{"establishmentid":"1913","name":"Happy's Pizza #4","address":"16850 Schaefer Hwy","zipcode":"48235"},{"establishmentid":"1426","name":"Burger King #5771","address":"13600 W McNichols Rd","zipcode":"48235"},{"establishmentid":"1895","name":"L. George's Coney Island ","address":"13635 W McNichols Rd","zipcode":"48235"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"48814","inspectionDate":"2019-08-19T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-08-19T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"4-302.12","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be provided and readily accessible for use in ensuring attainment and maintenance of FOOD temperatures as specified under Chapter 3. (Pf)   \r\n(B) A TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE with a suitable small-diameter probe that is designed to measure the temperature of thin masses shall be provided and readily accessible to accurately measure the temperature in thin FOODS such as MEAT patties and FISH filets. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food thermometer(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"2-402.11","violationDescription":"FOOD EMPLOYEES shall wear hair restraints such as hats, hair coverings or nets, beard restraints, and clothing that covers body hair, that are designed and worn to effectively keep their hair from contacting exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE or SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Hair restraint","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not worn on head/hair","subProblem":"","location":"EMPLOYEE(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-501.111","violationDescription":"The presence of insects, rodents, and other pests shall be controlled to minimize their presence on the PREMISES.  by:\r\n(A) Routinely inspecting incoming shipments of FOOD and supplies; \r\n(B) Routinely inspecting the PREMISES for evidence of pests;\r\n(C) Using methods, if pests are found, such as trapping devices or other means of pest control as specified.(Pf) \r\n(D) Eliminating harborage conditions. \r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Pest(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not performed","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"44440","inspectionDate":"2018-12-12T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-304.15","violationDescription":"(A) SINGLE-USE gloves shall be used for one task only and discarded when      damaged, soiled, or when interruptions occur in the operation. (P)\r\n\r\n(B) Slash-resistant and cloth gloves shall be used in direct contact only with FOOD that is subsequently cooked. Gloves used with ready-to-eat foods shall be smooth,   durable and non-absorbant.\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Single-use glove(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Used for multiple purposes","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Grill","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-12-12T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Gloves shall only be used for one purpose and then disposed."},{"violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-12-12T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\r\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \r\n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Non-food contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Grill","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean"},{"violationCode":"6-202.11","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise approved, light bulbs shall be shielded, coated, or otherwise shatter-resistant in areas where there is exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Light shielding","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Missing","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."}]},{"inspectionid":"42792","inspectionDate":"2018-07-05T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Hot food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"COOKING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-07-05T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store above 135 degrees F."}]},{"inspectionid":"40999","inspectionDate":"2017-12-07T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"SANITIZER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-07-05T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"3-501.17","violationDescription":"(A)  READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared and held refrigerated for more than 24 hours in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT  shall be clearly marked at the time of preparation to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n(B)  A container of refrigerated, commercially prepared READY-TO-EAT POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be clearly marked, at the time the original container is opened in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n\r\nA date marking system that does not exceed 7 days, including date of preparation, or opening is to be used. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"In house prepared ready-to-eat potentially hazardous  food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Without date of consumption marking","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Establishment shall provide a clear date marking system."},{"violationCode":"3-501.17","violationDescription":"(A)  READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared and held refrigerated for more than 24 hours in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT  shall be clearly marked at the time of preparation to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n(B)  A container of refrigerated, commercially prepared READY-TO-EAT POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be clearly marked, at the time the original container is opened in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n\r\nA date marking system that does not exceed 7 days, including date of preparation, or opening is to be used. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Commercially processed ready to eat potentially hazardous food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Improperly date marked","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Establishment shall provide a clear date marking system."}]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2020-05-29T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"5332"}}